sbr-technologies.com 2010-11-30

# Privacy policy

SBR Technologies is dedicated to your service and protect your sole privacy by taking responsible steps. As a provider of complete website solutions we need to have some of your personal data like personal phone number, email id, billing information and other usage detail. SBR Technologies promises you to keep your secrecy to the fullest and not lend, rent or sell it without your sole consent. We know how to keep the trust of our clientele.

Collection of Information 

While taking up a project, the necessary information we need to collect is your personal contact and bank account details to carry on professional dealing. Apart from that our system also log the IP address, website browser type, visited site, time spent on each pages and redirection approach of a certain visitor with most commonly applicable rules and regulations. 

The time you register SBR Technologies for our product and services we ask for your personal information as we don't like to work with anonymous business partners. 

Verification Method 

SBR admin collect your personal data while registering to our site. Our data analyzers verify the given information to ensure your authenticity. We keep this information to our database for future correspondences. If you find any inaccuracy to our database you can contact us instantly and we will take immediate measures for its correction. We also provide instant alteration service for necessary amendments. 

Authorized Accessibility 

We provide you complete accessibility to your personal information so that you can have necessary alteration whenever needed. If any technical or administrative hindrances come into way, we immediately take care of that and notify you about the systemic error. Such errors might often restrict your data admittance for a certain period of time which is taken care of and dealt with utmost care and responsibility for immediate restoration of the personalized program. 

Privacy and Discretion

We strive to provide you the best internet security experiences. SBR Technologies use advanced procedure to protect your personal information. To ensure a safeguard we imply authorized accessibility to individual data management. Your personal information is taken to carry forward business transaction systematically with SBR Technologies and with some of our business partners. 

We limit access to your personal database with password security service and allow authentic admittance with your consent. SBR Technologies never share personal identifying information with a third party at any circumstance. 

Disclaimer

We might change our privacy policies to deal with your personal information; and in that case you will be notified accordingly. Feel free to contact us to get answer of your further queries about SBR Privacies.
